createfreeblogs.com 2008-12-09

# Create Free Blogs ~ Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  
Last Updated Oct 2007

We recognize that privacy is an important issue, so we design and operate our services with the protection of your privacy in mind. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use our website, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard it.

The following principles apply to the personally identifying information we ask for and that you provide. "Personally identifying information" is information that individually identifies you, such as your name, physical address or email address.

Data collection  
Some of our services and/or information requests may require you to register for an account and/or provide personal information. We will use that information to provide the service or fulfill the information you requested.

Cookies  
Upon your first visit to our site, a cookie may be sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. A "cookie" is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. We sometimes use cookies to improve the quality of our service and to better understand how people interact with us. We do this by storing user preferences in cookies and by tracking user trends and patterns of how people search. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some of our features or services may not function properly without cookies.

Information sharing  
We do not rent or sell your personally identifying information to other companies or individuals, unless we have your consent. We may share such information in any of the following limited circumstances:

-We have your consent.

-We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

-We conclude that we are required by law or have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of our company, its users or the public.

If you have an account, we may share the information submitted under your account among all of our services in order to provide you with a seamless experience and to improve the quality of our services. We will not disclose your account information to other people or non-affiliated companies, except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy or with your consent.

We may store and process personal information collected on our site in the United States or any other country in which we or our agents maintain facilities. By using our services, you consent to the transfer of your information among these facilities, including those located outside your country.

In the event of a transfer of ownership of our company, such as acquisition by or merger with another company, we will provide notice before any personally identifying information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We may share aggregated information with others.

Information security  
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data.

We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.

Updating your information  
We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personally identifying information for many of our services. If you have any problems updating your information, please contact us at via the link below.

Links  
Our site includes links to other websites that might be useful to our visitors. These websites are developed by people over whom we exercise no control. These other sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information.

Changes to this Policy  
Please note this Privacy Policy will change from time to time. We expect most such changes to be minor, but there may be changes that are more significant. Regardless, we will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice. Each version will be noted at the top of the page.

If you have any additional questions, please feel to contact us any time at the link below.
